welcome to STS for getting set for the
欢迎来到STS为
clips video so the nagas TS for for
剪辑视频，以便将nagas TS用于
eclipse you need to go to spring do
月食你需要去春季吗
slash tools for web page it lists
列出的网页斜线工具
sprinkles for downloads for various 80s
大量下载供80年代使用
you'd have to find spring tools for for
您必须找到用于的spring tool
eclipse there is a number of download
蚀有很多下载
links right under it for various
它下面的各种链接
platforms they work on Mac so I have
他们可以在Mac上使用的平台
done loaded and installed STS for
完成加载和安装的STS
eclipse for Mac version I just quickly
Eclipse for Mac版本我很快
started this is the splash screen for
开始，这是启动画面
STS war and we're gonna open up a brand
STS战争，我们要建立一个品牌
new getting started workspace there is
有新的入门工作区
nothing in that workspace so let's just
该工作区中没有任何东西，所以让我们
wait until it opens up we can create a
等到它打开，我们可以创建一个
new boot project and it using spring
新的引导项目，它使用spring
starter project visit it's bad by spring
初学者项目访问在春天之前很糟糕
initializer so let's click Next here
初始化程序，所以让我们单击“下一步”
let's pick a few starters for us we'll
让我们为我们选择一些入门者
do web actuator starter that's to see
做网页执行器启动器，看看
life ins information our source code and
生活信息我们的源代码和
dev tools to be able to reload the
开发工具，以便能够重新加载
running app when when the source code
运行应用程序时的源代码
changes so let's wait until the project
变化，让我们等到项目
is created and dependents has downloaded
已创建，并且家属已下载
by LCD so it's done now we can browse
通过LCD完成，现在我们可以浏览
through the project it just has a long
通过这个项目，它有很长的时间
one simple class to launch springboard
一个简单的类来启动跳板
application we can launch it we can
我们可以启动它的应用程序
launch this application using this boot
使用此启动启动此应用程序
dashboard so let's do it now it's good
仪表板，所以现在就开始做吧
take a bit of time to to create a
花一点时间来创建一个
logical figuration for the first time so
逻辑上是第一次
it's starting out right now and it's up
它现在开始并且上升
and running now as you could solve from
并立即运行，您可以从中解决
this green arrow facing up we could
这个绿色的箭头朝上，我们可以
create a cross mapping because there is
创建交叉映射，因为存在
nothing in this application really so
在这个应用程序中什么都没有
let's call our controller REST API and
我们将其称为控制器REST API，
I'm afraid it with the rest controller
我怕剩下的控制器
now let's create a request mapping so it
现在让我们创建一个请求映射
gets mapping and we're gonna use a code
获取映射，我们将使用代码
snippet for it and it's going to be the
片段，它将是
root URL we can return the string and we
根URL，我们可以返回字符串，我们
need any parameters and the string we
需要任何参数和字符串我们
return is going to be hello string you
返回将是你好字符串你
did you miss me so let's take care of
你想我吗，让我们照顾
the imports save it so the dev tools
导入文件将其保存，因此开发工具
should reload our app with the changes
应该用更改重新加载我们的应用
we've made and we should see the green
我们已经完成，我们应该看到绿色
box around get mapping when it becomes
周围的盒子会变成映射
life so this is a life request might be
生活，所以这是生活要求，可能是
now this is electric my snacking URL so
现在这是我的零食网址，所以
we get to it yeah works we can also try
我们做到了，是的，我们也可以尝试
well we can stop the application and try
好吧，我们可以停止该应用程序并尝试
some other things we can while imports
我们可以在导入时进行其他操作
and getting started spring guides using
并开始使用Spring 指南
import getting started content wizard
导入入门内容向导
so let's if it lasts various sample
让我们来看看它能持续各种样本
projects for various aspects of spring
春季各个方面的项目
so we could look for something look for
所以我们可以寻找一些寻找
reactive for example and try reactive
例如反应式，然后尝试反应式
rest service so you could try their
休息服务，所以你可以尝试他们
initial code set or a complete code set
初始代码集或完整的代码集
which is already done for you as well
这已经为您完成了
you can open or it not open the the page
您可以打开或不打开页面
for this guide so in the trunk the
对于本指南，在后备箱中
complete satin is going to be maven
完整的缎子将成为行家
project so I'll just click on finish so
项目，所以我只点击完成，
ideally it should create the project for
理想情况下，它应该为
us and we can navigate through it and
我们，我们可以浏览它，
you can see that there is it they're all
您可以看到只有它们
recreated the functional style alter
重新创建了功能样式alter
with the handler for for the color
与颜色的处理程序
across my thing which is here method and
在我的东西这是方法
we can start the stop using the boot
我们可以使用靴子开始停止
dashboard again and we can navigate to
仪表板再次，我们可以导航到
the hello endpoints as well just to see
你好端点也只是看
if that
如果说
works now here it is stop this app and
现在在这里工作，这是停止此应用程序和
we can go on the further and create a
我们可以继续并创建一个
complete demo application like this
像这样的完整演示应用程序
spring pet clinic and the reference map
春季宠物诊所和参考图
each opened the page it's going to be
每个打开的页面将是
maven project and click finish and the
Maven项目，然后单击完成，然后
project will be created and you because
项目将被创建，您因为
navigates you could explore this project
导航您可以探索这个项目
a bit and we could see if we could put a
一点，我们可以看看是否可以放一个
breakpoint and stop here for example
断点并在此停止
let's type the project and debug mode
让我们输入项目和调试模式
again takes some time to create launch
再次需要一些时间来创建启动
configuration it's being stacked it up
配置它正在堆叠起来
so when when the app is launched in
因此，当应用启动时
debugger is attached you would see a
调试器已连接，您将看到一个
little bit different icon as a bug on it
一点不同的图标作为它的错误
this is it and we could navigate to a
就是这样，我们可以导航到
goodly to the rest hand point or the
良好的休息点或
alike request mapping URL like this
像这样的请求映射URL
where I stopped at the breakpoints I
我在断点停下来的地方
believe yes so this is that this is a
相信是的，所以这是一个
quick cast yes for getting started with
快速投放是，可以开始使用
eclipse video thank you for watching
蚀视频谢谢您的观看
you
您